[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Stan"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 42, "question": "And if you were advising Charlie Sheen now, what would you do to try and perhaps rebuild the bridge that's crashed around him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", ",", "WDT", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "POS", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 43, "answer": "You know, Stan's a very good friend, and he did the right thing.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Warner Brothers", "CBS", "Les Moonves"], "PERSON": ["Chuck Laurie"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 54, "question": "He's almost playing the Hollywood power game in his own way, and doing it in a way no one's done before, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 55, "answer": "Well, he's certainly playing a power game, but he's playing it with people like Warner Brothers, CBS, Les Moonves, Chuck Laurie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", ",", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 68, "question": "You wouldn't deny taking hits of cocaine?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 69, "answer": "Well, no, of course not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 92, "question": "What did you make of the whole interview in context?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 93, "answer": "I just felt -- I felt a heavy heart.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Bob"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", ",", "NN", "CD", ",", "IN", "NNP", "VBD", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 127, "question": "And if that private life is not adversely affecting his professional working environment, and it didn't seem to be much, then what's the problem?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 128, "answer": "Well, I think there is a problem because, number one, as Bob said earlier, it was spiraling out of control.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VB", "IN", "DT", "RB", "CC", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 143, "question": "I mean, do you look at a guy and think his life's in danger?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "VBP", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 144, "answer": "You know, I try to -- I tend to just focus on the here and now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", ",", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "Does he take any personal responsibility for the deaths of his people right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "When we ask about that, though, he says no, no reasonable person would shoot peaceful protesters.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 211, "question": "Does he think he can just ride this out?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 212, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 222, "question": "And if that is the case, is this good for America and the west, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 223, "answer": "Well, to your question about whether it's anti- American or whether it's the people here themselves, it is the people in this region themselves.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 240, "question": "Harvey, how are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 241, "answer": "Piers, I'm -- couldn't be better.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Does it get better in Hollywood than being the guy that produced \"the movie\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "``", "DT", "NN", "''", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, I was executive producer, but I had a bit to do with it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "What happens in there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "No kneecap.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 278, "question": "What's the business of turning around an Oscar campaign?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 279, "answer": "First of all, \"Social Network\" is a fabulous movie.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 282, "question": "But how did you kill it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 283, "answer": "I have to win for me, and I didn't kill them.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Golden Globe"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "PRP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", ",", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 300, "question": "What was the key thing that you felt you had to do to get this film back on its tracks?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 301, "answer": "I think losing the Golden Globe for best picture for me, feeling that that was something that we could win was the absolute thing that instead of making me quit like a lot of people said, absolutely motivated me the complete opposite way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "RB", "CD", "NN", "TO", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What are the key things you had to change?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "There's only one thing to really do.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 315, "question": "How important is it to get your front people out there selling that movie?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBZ", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 316, "answer": "It's important to get it -- a movie connected to an audience, and it's important in an Oscar campaign.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 324, "question": "ORGAN: When you heard the words \"best movie , 'The King's Speech',\" what did you feel?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "``", "JJS", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NNP", "POS", ",", "''", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 325, "answer": "I was elated.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "One of the greatest moments of your life?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CD", "IN", "DT", "JJS", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "It's fantastic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 344, "question": "What did you make -- what do you make of the Charlie Sheen story from a position of being a top producer in Hollywood?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 345, "answer": "I worked with Charlie Sheen.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"], "LOCATION": ["Hollywood"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 357, "question": "ORGAN: You think so?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 358, "answer": "Absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "``", "NNP", "NNP", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", ".", "''"], "qSentId": 378, "question": "Would you hire Charlie Sheen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 379, "answer": "I'd hire Charlie Sheen to do \"Scary Movie 4, 5, 6, 7.\"", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Charlie Sheen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Would you put him in a series maybe or no?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "I don't make TV series, so thank god.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "RB", "CD", "CC", "CD", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 400, "question": "How many Oscars have you got at home?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 401, "answer": "I have about -- probably 15 or 20 at home.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 419, "question": "OK?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NN", "."], "aSentId": 420, "answer": "You've got your work cut out there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "``", "NNP", "CD", "''", "."], "qSentId": 429, "question": "If you could make the ultimate movie for people dead or alive, you know, director, producer, leading man, leading lady, who would it be?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "VBG", "NN", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 430, "answer": "Well, I own a book called \"Mila 18\".", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Hal Wallace", "Walter Mirsh"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "VBG", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", ":", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "And who would produce it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Probably producing it would be Hal Wallace and there's actually somebody alive who is young -- a young man at 87 years old, his name is Walter Mirsh.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Katherine Hepburn"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 445, "question": "Best actor and actress you've ever seen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["JJS", "NN", "CC", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "."], "aSentId": 446, "answer": "I think Katherine Hepburn could play the leading lady.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 448, "question": "And the man?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 449, "answer": "Both Hepburns could play that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Libya", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 492, "question": "What's the simple answer?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 493, "answer": "The simple answer is if you don't tell the story from both sides, you will never understand everything we're watching in Libya, Egypt, you know, et cetera.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 523, "question": "Was that your intention, was it designed to inspire people more than anything else?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "RBR", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 524, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", ",", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 531, "question": "And she got -- she married four times and I think you moved how -- 17 times in 12 years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "WRB", ":", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 532, "answer": "By the time I was 18, yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "RB", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "DT", ":", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 539, "question": "But the sexual abuse?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 540, "answer": "The sexual abuse, listen, when you're -- when you're 10 years old and you try to tell your parents, first of all the -- the -- the perpetrator says, you know, no one will believe you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 549, "question": "So what does she make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 550, "answer": "She said it's pretty personal.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 581, "question": "But did -- did part of you think I should talk about this before other people do as your star rises?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBD", ":", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "No, it wasn't that.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", ":", "RB", ":", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 583, "question": "Was that at the back of our mind as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 584, "answer": "Not -- not -- not with the abuse stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "I mean, were you aware that what he was doing was wrong?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "ROWN: Oh, absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "qSentId": 622, "question": "Why was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 623, "answer": "Embarrassment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 656, "question": "Well what are your thoughts to the man that abused you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "WP", "VBP", "PRP$", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 657, "answer": "Well, I've moved on.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "DT", "RB", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 666, "question": "Strange feeling, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 667, "answer": "Yes, a little bit yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "RB", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ":"], "qSentId": 679, "question": "And how bad was that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "JJ", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 680, "answer": "It was -- well, obviously you read the book --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 695, "question": "He punching you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 696, "answer": "Yes, yes, we'd be kind of banging on each other.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["JJ", "."], "qSentId": 703, "question": "And the judge, I think, is very smart, isn't he?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 704, "answer": "Brilliant.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Judge Zolf"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 705, "question": "Tell me again what he does?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 706, "answer": "Well, it was Judge Zolf (ph) from Salem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", ",", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 748, "question": "Do you think he regrets what he did?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 749, "answer": "He -- we were out about three weeks ago, went to breakfast and he said -- he looked me right in the eye and he said you know, I just want to say I'm sorry.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 761, "question": "But I can see in you now that that makes you emotional, doesn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "WDT", "IN", "VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 762, "answer": "Yes, Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 768, "question": "Is he proud of you now, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 769, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Aryana"]}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", ":", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 788, "question": "Was your mom there as well?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP$", "NN", "EX", "IN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 789, "answer": "Yes, mom's right next to Aryana (ph) absolutely.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 802, "question": "Does it have your head on it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 803, "answer": "I wish it did.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 808, "question": "It's been a very emotional 20 minutes, hasn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 809, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 827, "question": "What does that mean?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 828, "answer": "It meant nothing.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 845, "question": "For what?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 846, "answer": "You know what I'm asking you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 853, "question": "Could you be tempted to run for president?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 854, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 861, "question": "What do -- what do you make of what's happening in the Middle East in the context of America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 862, "answer": "Well, I'm hopeful because people are obviously seeking freedom and democracy.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", ":", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 865, "question": "When you see what's going on in the Middle East, where it's happening in an evolutionary way, through the grass roots or the people themselves, isn't it a better way for America to go in the future?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "DT", "JJR", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 866, "answer": "Well, I think every -- every situation, you have to take it on its own merits.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East", "America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 888, "question": "That's it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 889, "answer": "That's it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110301pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NN", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 891, "question": "How about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 892, "answer": "OK, whatever.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]